Anton Bogomazov

Software Engineer

Summary

As a Software Engineer with 2 years of experience, I specialize in Kotlin and web development and have solid Java knowledge. I am a constant learner and enjoy delving into technical details. In my work, I follow the Boy Scout rule and offer solutions for improving code quality. I am rational and prioritize the benefits of the project over my own personal preferences. I also practice extreme programming techniques such as TDD and pair programming, and regularly provide feedback on my work through frequent PRs and detailed task decomposition.

Experience

Senior Software Engineer @ Setronica

Aug 2022 - Present

- Analyzed the current system and suggested improvements to architecture and user experience, making it more stable.
- Developed new features for B2B marketplace, including a supplier-buyer chat.
- Maintained a mature system with multiple programming languages for both backend and frontend.
- · Shared best practices of designing systems and programming techniques.

Lead Software Engineer @ Beeline

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022

- Led a team of 6 people in the development of a service for managing the personal data of clients, their agreements, and services
- Delivered and deployed the first releases
- Improved the CI/CD pipelines and streamlined team processes.

Software Engineer @ Domclick

Dec 2020 - Apr 2022

- Designed and implemented operations with pledge property and mortgage
- Improved DX by automating everyday engineering tasks such as artifacts delivery
- Tuned service performance to increase the availability
- Shared knowledge and expertise with new team members
- Explored experimental technologies, including reactor coroutines adapter, GraalVM, and native images, and assessed their compatibility with the current system.

Education

Computer Science @ Ecole42 Moscow

Dec 2019 - Jan 2021

 École 42 is a private institution of higher education in computer science that does not have traditional professors and is based on peer-to-peer and project-based learning.

- abogomazov.dev@gmail.com
- abogomazov.com
- github.com/anton-bogomazov
- linkedin.com/in/abogomazov

Skills

Design

OOP principles and patterns, Functional Design

Programming Languages

Java, Kotlin, C, JavaScript

Frameworks

Spring, Ktor, Compose

Databases

Postgres, Mongo, Hibernate, jOOQ, Exposed, Liquibase

Testing

Junit, Kotest, Mockito, WireMock

Message Brokers

RabbitMQ, Kafka

DevOps

Docker, Kubernetes, GitHub Actions

Monitoring

Grafana, ELK, Prometheus, Zabbix

Projects

Algorithms and Data structures

Algorithms and Data structures written in (almost) human language

NFT collection generator

Architectural playground built around fun idea of generating sets of images

Personal Website

Personal Website built on Kotlin Compose

Languages

German

English	Certified B2
Russian	Native

Α1